

#### IUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER · FRONT-FND DEVELOPER

33-20159 68 Avenue Langley BC Canada

□+1 778 751 7015 | ■ polyakovkate@gmail.com | ■ https://www.linkedin.com/in/kate-polyakov-8a105a202/

"Placed in between organizations and technology, I am committed and enthusiastic in what I do. Driven by great challenges and learning opportunities, I look forward to combining technical knowledge with interpersonal skills."

# **Summary**\_

I have been a passionate web developer since middle school where I was using Q-Basic and Pascal. In high school, I completed a two-year program in Information Technology. More recently, I finished the Full Stack Web developer bootcamp from the Londonappbrewery training centre, UK. One of my goals is continuous improvement of my web development expertise. My dream job is working in a competent and supportive web developing team that creates reliable and functional websites and applications that help achieving customers their goals. I would like to best utilize my abilities by generating maximum traffic to clients' web projects by showcasing high-quality SEO content, user- and mobile-friendly navigation and promotion to as many social media platforms as possible.

## Skills

**Programming** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, React, SQL, JSON

**DevOps** BigCommerce **Languages** English, Russian

# Work Experience\_

QE HOME Linen

Burnaby, BC

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Aug. 2021 - Sept. 2021

- Turn the creative team's designs into well-built HTML, CSS and JS
- · Optimize website features and pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Spot bugs and barriers to a smooth user experience and come up with practical solutions.

Self-Employed Vancouver, BC

WEB DEVELOPER Nov. 2019 - present

- · Developed websites.
- · Enhanced user experience and accomplish webpage objectives by creating site structure, navigation, page optimization.
- Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.

Belcom Communication Moscow, Russia

FINANCIAL ANALYST Mar. 2010 - Feb.2018

- Applied advanced IT and analytical skills and economic trend, business and industrial sector research to impact corporate decision making.
- Used mathematical formulas, statistical models and analytical techniques to assess information.
- · Provided technical support to increase policy impact through high-level economic and public policy advice and analysis.
- Conducted direct survey with target individuals and reviewed market data.

### **Education**

### Kemerovo State University

M.S. IN ECONOMICS 2003 - 2008

• Honors Diploma 4.75/5

# **Projects & Courses**

#### **TechWomen (Cohort 4) from ISSofBC**

Vancouver, Canada

Russia

Web Developer .

• TechWomen is a 9-month part-time pre-employment program funded by the Canadian Women's Foundation that offers newcomer women an entryway into Web Development and foundational skills towards a career in the tech industry. It is offered through ISSofBC with the support of partnering schools – Lighthouse Labs, CodeCore, BrainStation and Emily Carr University. The program includes occupational specific language training, an introduction to coding, front-end development and digital design through our partner tech schools, job readiness and soft skills training, and a practical component.

DECEMBER 13, 2021 KATE POLYAKOV · RÉSUMÉ

### **Emily Carr University of Art and Design**

Vancouver, Canada

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND WEB DESIGN

2021

• This course introduces the fundamentals of website design. Content includes technical and aesthetic issues of developing a website, such as writing code effective across multiple browsers and devices, and producing bandwidth-friendly graphics for site.

ADOBE FOR DESIGN + PRODUCTION 2021

• This course provides a comprehensive introduction to Adobe Creative Cloud, including Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign. As integrated software tools for the design and production of print and media assets, you will be introduced to topics including document layout, type-setting, vector and raster images for print and digital outputs. Gain basic knowledge of each program, and how they work together as an integrated toolkit.

The App Brewery

London, UK

WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

2020

• The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp Full-stack. Throughout this comprehensive course, we covered a massive amount of tools and technologies, including Front-End Web Development (HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap 4/5), Javascript ES6, DOM Manipulation, jQuery, Bash-Command, Git, GitHub and Version Control, Backend Web Development, Node.js, NPM, Express.js, EJS, REST, APIs, Databases, SQLMongoose, Authentication, Firebase, React.js, React Hooks, Web Design, Deployment with GitHub Pages, Heroku and MongoDB Atlas.

## **Additional Information**

**Travelling** U.S. Visa and driving license